PROPHECY TIME
You're a man.
Your affection is dead.
This is giving you loneliness.
Yes, Man of God.
Anybody that looks at you would say "hey" but you don't have affection.
Yes, I struggle too much. You're right, Man of God.
You don't have affection. Anybody that looks at you - you are a beautiful lady, beautiful woman -
they want to marry you but you don't have affection.
They would marry you, after getting married, they would realise that the affection is dead.
That is the challenge you are facing.
Yes, Man of God. You are very, very correct.
You are very, very right.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
PROPHECY CONFIRMATION
My name is Obimma, and this is my lovely husband.
What the man of God said is very, very correct.
The problem started when I got married.
I got married at a very tender age - I was a virgin.
That very night was not easy for me.
I cried the whole way through.
When my mother-in-law noticed what was happening,
she called me aside and cuddled me.
She had to mix up some things that would help me calm down.
It didn't end there.
From that very moment, I developed phobia with anything that had to do with sex and being with a man.
Because after that day, I tried several times but I couldn't give in.
Everything was totally lost - completely out.
Anything that had to do with intercourse or being married as a couple - I didn't really like it.
It kept going on and on.
It kept affecting me so much, even after years of marriage.
In fact, we were just existing because I always wanted to be out of the house or taking a trip.
At times, I would use it against him.
I would say, "Maybe when I come back from London, we will continue", and I would go.
During that time I stayed for two years and came back again.
Then I said, "Okay, I have to go to South Africa".
I went and stayed for five years, then I came back again.
It wasn't only towards my husband; it was also to other men.
I would tend to be so aggressive towards people.
They would see me and like me.
There was no way that I would be moving around and not see 3 to 5 men staring at me.
At times, if they stared too long, I would ask them, "What for?"
It was really affecting me.
It would affect my business so badly.
For someone to even make it, a male counterpart would have to come in
but I was always so aggressive towards them.
I forgot about marriage.
I decided to go into business.
I was just married to my business, married to everything that I was doing.
It was not as if I was building a house or anything but I saw that business as a way to move away,
as a way to stay out and not have any form of marriage.
The affection was totally lost.
It was a very long time before I conceived.
On my first and only conception, God blessed me so much.
By then we had been watching Emmanuel TV because we heard about it in South Africa.
Even on the day of conception, I was pushing my husband away.
He was always begging.
He would say, "Mommy, come now."
I would say, "No, not tonight".
I would say, "I'm tired - I'm just coming back".
But that night, I had gone so long without giving him anything, that I said, "Okay, let me do it".
Even when he came, I said, "Do this thing fast and let me go".
When I conceived, it was months after the conception before I realised I was pregnant
because I didn't know thatjust one short time could get me pregnant.
As God would have it, I delivered twins - a boy and a girl.
Mr & Mrs Obimma
Prophecy Confirmation
Even before I came here, I was hoping for another kind of prophecy.
When the man of God told me that, I realised it was the root of my problem.
Indeed, it was the root of my problem.
Loneliness had come in, boredom - he would ask me out and I would say, "No".
I wouldn't go anywhere; I would just stay indoors.
If I wasn't doing business or had to draw money, I didn't want to go out
because I didn't want to be around anybody who would be frolicking around me.
Now, after seeing my bundles of joy, I wanted to conceive again.
You mean immediately the man of God gave you that prophecy,
you just saw it as a channel of hope?
When what you are not expecting is thrown at you -
I was so overwhelmed because it was as if someone somewhere who knew me
had told the man of God what my problem was.
You can't imagine the kind of feelings I had inside me.
So the problem affected your marriage to the extent that after that first child,
you tried to conceive again but because of that lack of affection, you could not go ahead.
I still couldn't go ahead. When it was time for us to meet,
I would say to myself, "Okay, tonight I will try" and I would prepare myself
but when the time came, I would still push him away.
But immediately the man of God gave that prophecy,
can you tell us what God did in your life?
After the man of God gave me the prophecy, I became so light.
That very day, I was set free and felt as if I was empty and light.
I knew something had left me.
My name is Mr Isaac Obimma.
We know you would also like to introduce the person standing beside you.
She is my lovely wife.
Your lovely wife. Hallelujah.
When she came back home that Sunday, she told me the prophecy.
I already knew what the problem was.
For one reason or another, I couldn't watch Emmanuel TV that Sunday but today,
I was able to capture the prophecy, which was exactly the problem we were having.
I'm here today to testify that the prophecy was a hundred percent correct.
Mr & Mrs Obimma
Prophecy Confirmation
We just want to ask you briefly as a husband,
how did that problem of lack of affection affect you as a man?
Well, what it calls for is patience and talk to God.
He always resolves all issues.
While all this was going on, I knew that one day the end would come and here we are today.
I thank God.
Hallelujah!
We thank God.
Madam, after that prophetic message, we saw how the man of God delivered you
in the power of the Holy Ghost.
Looking at your husband, how do you now feel towards your husband?
I feel wonderful - so good.
Even when I met him --- he is the one 'giving me a tough time' now.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Put your hands together for Jesus for the restoration of this marriage!
At a particular time, I went to him and laid my hand on him; I wanted to lie ---
He was like, "Hey, what is going on?"
He was really surprised, after many years of lack of affection in the marriage.
Because I did not really allow it before.
Hallelujah. We thank God for the wonderful restoration of this marriage.
What advice do you want to give to the world
concerning what God has done in your life through the power of prophecy?
Okay, I will use my own case as an example.
This particular thing has destroyed lots of marriages, many homes.
I was just so fortunate to have this kind of a man,
because it's not every man that can stand that.
I know what I'm saying because I'm the one that caused all the havoc.
It's not every man that can just 'starve' like that - let me just put it in that way.
Or you leave the man for a long while; you are abroad and he is there.
Even when he came to visit, there was a particular time he came and we didn't even do anything.
It was like, "Why did I even come here in the first place?"
So my advice to people like that is to seek the face of God; something is wrong somewhere.
As soon as I got delivered, I got myself back.
Hallelujah. Let us put our hands together once again for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
My advice: It's not the best to wish to any man but when it comes your way,
rest your hope on God. It's as simple as that.
Hallelujah! We give glory to God Almighty for this wonderful blessing He has granted onto this family.
I want to advise you that now God Almighty has done this wonderful thing,
continue to make His word the standard for your life and for your marriage
and we know more and more blessings are on the way. Hallelujah!
Hallelujah. We give glory to God Almighty!
Let us put our hands together once again for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.